(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-09-30T03:19:59.905524",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
恋
Lyrics, Music: 星野源
[Song: Koi (Love) - Lyrics & Music: Gen Hoshino]
営みの 街が暮れたら 色めき
Once the busy streets are painted by the twilight,
風たちは運ぶわ カラスと人々の群れ
The winds carry away the crows and the crowd of people.
意味なんか ないさ暮らしがあるだけ
There is no special meaning, there's just daily life.
ただ腹を空かせて 君の元へ帰るんだ
Simply getting hungry, and returning to your side.
物心ついたらふっと 見上げて思うことが
Ever since I was old enough to understand, I would look up and think:
この世にいる誰も 二人から
Everyone in this world started from two people.
胸の中にあるもの
The thing inside my heart...
いつか見えなくなるもの
The thing that will one day fade from sight...
それは側にいること いつも思い出して
That is being by your side, always remember that.
君の中にあるもの
The thing inside of you...
距離の中にある鼓動
The heartbeat within the distance...
恋をしたのは あなたの
The one I fell in love with is yours...
指の交ざり 頬の香り
Intertwined fingers, the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Go beyond husband and wife.
醜いと 秘めた想いは 色づき
The hidden feelings I thought were ugly begin to color...
白鳥は運ぶわ 当たり前を 変えながら
The swans carry them, changing what we take for granted.
恋せずにいられないな 似た顔の虚構にも
I can't help but fall in love, even with a fiction of a similar face.
愛が生まれるのは 一人から
Love is born from a single person.
胸の中にあるもの
The thing inside my heart...
いつか見えなくなるもの
The thing that will one day fade from sight...
それは側にいること いつも思い出して
That is being by your side, always remember that.
君の中にあるもの
The thing inside of you...
距離の中にある鼓動
The heartbeat within the distance...
恋をしたのは あなたの
The one I fell in love with is yours...
指の交ざり 頬の香り
Intertwined fingers, the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Go beyond husband and wife.
泣き顔も
Even your crying face...
黙る夜も
Even the silent nights...
揺れる笑顔も いつまでも
Even your waving smile, forever...
いつまでも
Forever and ever.
胸の中にあるもの
The thing inside my heart...
いつか見えなくなるもの
The thing that will one day fade from sight...
それは側にいること いつも思い出して
That is being by your side, always remember that.
君の中にあるもの
The thing inside of you...
距離の中にある鼓動
The heartbeat within the distance...
恋をしたのは あなたの
The one I fell in love with is yours...
指の交ざり 頬の香り
Intertwined fingers, the scent of your cheek.
夫婦を超えてゆけ
Go beyond husband and wife.
二人を超えてゆけ
Go beyond the two of us.
一人を超えてゆけ
Go beyond being a single person.
Yeah!
みなさん！
Everyone!
みなさん、みなさん、みなさん、hey hey!
Everyone, everyone, everyone, hey hey!
What's up everybody!
Welcome!
Solo order.
Yes. Uh...
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
Yeah!
自己紹介、自己紹介！Introduction!
Introductions, introductions! Introduction!
All right, well, Senpai of us all.
Ina?
Yeah?
Really? Does that really count?
Senpai by like, what, an hour? Half an hour or so?
Yeah.
All righty, fine. So be it.
みなさん、it is I, Mori Calliope of HoloMyth.
Everyone, it is I, Mori Calliope of HoloMyth.
What's up everybody!
I do a lot of things, and I've been here a while.
Lost child. Four's my favorite number, but six is good too.
My go.
My turn.
Come here.
Here, here, come here, come here, come here.
Anyway, よろしく。And who's next?
Anyway, pleased to meet you. And who's next?
Who's next?
Kikiriki!
I am Takanashi Kiara from Hololive Myth!
How's it going? It's six years!
And... and...
I am surrounded by myth, myth, myth, myth, myth.
Myth, myth.
That's my introduction. I still don't have anything in particular.
My six years!
Now, what about you? Do you have a special introduction?
Yes she does, I'm ready for it.
Wah!
Wah! Wah!
Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone!
Ina'nis, of Hololive Myth.
Yo!
On this wonderful day!
Wow!
She was shaking her legs earlier. She was scared.
I was not!
大丈夫、大丈夫、よしよし。
It's okay, it's okay, there, there.
I was not!
It's gonna be okay.
Just don't dance too hard, you know? If you dance too hard, you're gonna fall.
Yeah.
Okay, everybody, congratulations! Six years!
Shake, shake, shake hands.
And check it out. After all this time, we also have...
We've all done live shows.
Oh, yeah!
And we're in the solo outfits!
Solo outfits, yes!
So much done in the six years, huh?
Done a lot, huh?
そうだね。
That's true.
I mean, I feel like six years ago, we never would have even thought that we could do that.
Yeah. Do you guys still remember the very first time we met each other on Discord?
Ah.
Yeah, it was weird. It was weird.
The introduction channel? Where like, everybody typed like a paragraph about themselves?
Yeah.
Yeah. And you didn't mention drawing at all, so we were all surprised!
She was hiding it even from us!
Well, that made it even more impressive.
Yeah.
そうだよ。So, this stream is supposed to celebrate our six years together.
That's right. So, this stream is supposed to celebrate our six years together.
Six!
And we have a hashtag for that too, right here.
MythSixYears.
Use it. Use it a lot.
On Twitter, etc.
Capture your favorite moments and share them with us, 'cause we look at that stuff, you know?
We love it.
Oh, after six years, her hips...
She's dancing...
Hips, okay.
Hips for you guys.
Okay, okay, okay. And we want you guys to take pictures of them.
Yeah.
Okay!
Beautiful pictures because not only are we wearing our beautiful outfits, but we also have this beautiful stage, right?
Yeah! High up in the sky. And, and, and...
I get a feeling that the seasons will change!
Yeah!
Depending upon the songs that we sing.
That's, that's probably true.
And we, we already showed them a little bit.
A little bit of the seasons.
With the first song that we performed, Koi!
Koi!
Which, I like that we're doing this one because we did a song cover for it too.
We did.
And it was really good. I really like how it turned out. There were all these cute scenes with us like cooking together and hanging out.
Yeah, yeah, it was cool.
Such a cute scene.
No.
No, I don't want that.
Lollipop? I'm not into lollipops.
You have your own lollipop, you already licked it. I don't want it.
She found out.
Gaki, gaki. We got to perform, we can't eat too much candy.
Brat, brat. We got to perform, we can't eat too much candy.
Yeah, but, after, it doesn't matter.
そうだよ。
That's right.
She's supposed to be this sassy lost child that we have here, huh?
Yeah.
She feels small!
In our solo live outfits, she has never been this small in comparison before.
How tiny are you?
They nerfed my height!
This is so tiny.
Are you really this...
Are you really this tiny?
Like our gaki cousin, little cousin, or something like that.
Like our bratty cousin, little cousin, or something like that.
Are we her aunties, her mommies, or her sisters?
Can we go to...
I can't say this.
やめろ！
Stop it!
Can we go to pee...
...after this?
No, no, no, we can't. We have that at home.
But Ina-chan, you know what?
What?
At the end of this stream, we'll have a surprise for you and everybody else!
And you won't want to miss it, so make sure that you behave for the entire live.
Okay.
No, no!
No, so stay until the end.
Ina, stay until the end. Everybody is in there too, okay?
As you wish. You're safe this time, Kiara.
Anyway...
Alright!
What could it be?
What could it be? Ooh boy!
Let's go!
Alright, shall we?
Ina's song!
Yeah!
Let's do this!
Next song!
September
[Title: September]
辛し色のシャツ 追いながら
Chasing after your mustard-colored shirt,
飛び乗った電車のドア
I jumped onto the train as the doors were closing.
いけないと知りながら
Though I knew I shouldn't,
振り向けば隠れた
when I turned around, you hid from me.
街は色づいた クレヨンが
The city is colored like a crayon,
涙まで染めて走る
even my tears are stained as I run.
年上の人に会う
To meet a man older than you,
約束と知ってて
knowing you had made a promise.
September
そしてあなたは
And then you...
September
秋に変わった
turned into autumn.
夏の陽射しが弱まるように
Just like the summer sun weakens,
心に影が射した
a shadow has cast over my heart.
September
そして九月は
And then, September...
September
サヨナラの国
is the land of goodbyes.
解きかけてる愛の結び目
The knot of our love is coming undone,
涙が木の葉になる
and my tears turn into autumn leaves.
逢ってその人に頼みたい
I want to meet that person and ask her
彼のこと返してねと
to give him back to me.
でも駄目ね きのうの朝
But it's no use; yesterday morning
唇も凍りつく
even my lips froze.
September
そしてあなたは
And then you...
September
秋に変わった
turned into autumn.
話すことさえなくなるなんて
For us to have nothing left to say to each other,
私にあきた証拠
is proof that you've grown tired of me.
September
そして九月は
And then, September...
September
サヨナラの国
is the land of goodbyes.
巡る季節の色どりの中
Amidst the colors of the changing seasons,
一番寂しい月
it is the loneliest month of all.
借りていたディクショナリー
The dictionary that I borrowed,
明日返すわ
I will return it tomorrow.
「ラブ」という言葉だけ
Only the word "Love,"
切り抜いたあと
I have cut it out.
それがグッバイ
That is my good-bye.
グッバイ
Good-bye.
September
そしてあなたは
And then you...
September
秋に変わった
turned into autumn.
私一人が傷つくことが
Me being the only one getting hurt...
残されたやさしさね
is the last piece of kindness you left me, isn't it?
September
そして九月は
And then, September...
September
サヨナラの国
is the land of goodbyes.
トリコロールの海辺の服も
Even the tricolor beachwear
二度と着ることはない
will never be worn again.
シュビドゥビドゥビドゥビドゥワーワー
Shu-bi-du-bi-du-bi-du-bi-du-wah-wah
September
ララララララララ
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la...
September
ララララララララ
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la...
ララララララララ...
BOW AND ARROW
[BOW AND ARROW] Lyrics, Music: Kenshi Yonezu
気がつけば 靴は汚れ
Before I knew it, my shoes were dirty,
錆び付いた諸刃伝う雨
rain trickling down the rusted double-edged blade.
憧れはそのままで
Leaving my admiration just as it is,
夢から目覚めた先には夢
beyond the dream I woke from is another dream.
聞こえたその泣き声
I heard that weeping voice,
消え入る手前のむせぶそれ
sobbing right before it fades away.
憧れのその先へ
Going beyond my admiration,
薄暗くなる君を見つけるため
just to find you fading into the dimness.
行け 行け
Go, go,
追いつけない速度で
at a speed no one can catch up to.
飛べ インパルス加速して
Fly, accelerating like an impulse.
行け きっとこの鼓動を
Go, surely to feel this heartbeat...
感じるために生まれてきたんだ
...is the reason I was born.
未来を掴んで 期待値を超えて
Seize the future, exceed all expectations,
額に刺さる風
as the wind strikes against your forehead.
今に見なよ きっと君の眩しさに
Just watch, surely everyone will realize...
誰もが気づくだろう
...how radiant you truly are.
相応しい声で 視線追い越して
With a fitting voice, overtaking their gazes,
虚空を超えて行け
fly across the empty void.
見違えていく君の指から今
Now, from your fingers that are changing...
手を放す
...I let go.
気がつけば謎は解かれ
Before I knew it, the mystery was solved,
木目ごと見慣れた板の上
on the familiar wooden floorboards.
あの頃焦がれたような大人になれたかな
Have I become the kind of adult I yearned to be back then?
そう君の苦痛は
Yes, your pain...
君が自分で選んだ傷みだ
...is a suffering you chose yourself.
そして掴んだその鍵も
And the key you grasped...
全て君のものだ
...it all belongs to you.
僕は夢になって
I became a dream...
君が掴んだ手のひらを通って強く引いた
passing through your grasping palm, pulling tightly.
今君は決して風に流されない
Now, you will never be swept away by the wind,
矢になって
becoming an arrow.
行け
Go,
決して振り向かないで
and never look back.
飛べ もう届かない場所へ
Fly, to a place no longer reachable.
行け 行け 行け
Go, go, go,
君はいつだって輝いていた
you were always shining bright.
未来を掴んで 期待値を超えて
Seize the future, exceed all expectations,
額に刺さる風
as the wind strikes against your forehead.
今に見なよ きっと君の眩しさに
Just watch, surely everyone will realize...
誰もが気づくだろう
...how radiant you truly are.
相応しい声で 視線追い越して
With a fitting voice, overtaking their gazes,
虚空を超えて行け
fly across the empty void.
見違えていく君の指から今
Now, from your fingers that are changing...
手を放す
...I let go.
はじめてのキスは
Our very first kiss...
涙の味がした
...tasted like tears.
まるでドラマみたいな恋
A love just like a TV drama,
見守るように
as if watching over us,
発車のベルが鳴った
the departure bell rang.
初めての恋が終わる時
[When My First Love Ends] Lyrics, Music: ryo
冷たい冬の風が
The cold winter wind...
頬をかすめる
...brushes past my cheek.
吐いた息で 両手をこする
I rub my hands together in my warm breath.
街はイルミネーション
The town is full of illuminations,
魔法をかけたみたい
as if a magic spell has been cast.
裸の街路樹 キラキラ
The bare roadside trees are sparkling.
どうしても言えなかった
No matter what, I couldn't say...
この気持ち おさえて
...repressing these feelings.
前から決めていたことだから
Since this was decided long ago,
これでいいの
this is for the best.
振り向かない
I won't look back.
ありがとう さよなら
Thank you, goodbye.
切ない片想い
This painful, unrequited love...
足を止めたら 思い出して しまう
if I stop my feet, I will end up remembering.
だから
That's why...
ありがとう さよなら
...thank you, goodbye.
泣いたりしないから
I won't cry anymore.
そう思った途端に ふわり
The moment I thought that, gently...
舞い降りてくる雪
...the falling snow...
触れたら 溶けて消えた
...melted and vanished as I touched it.
あー...
Ah...
足跡続く大通り
Along the broad street where footprints stretch...
寄り添ってる二人 楽しそう
the cuddling couple looks so happy.
ほら見て 初雪
Look! The first snow.
キミとあんな風に
I wanted to be like that...
なりたくて 初めて作った
...with you, so for the first time,
手編みのマフラー
I knitted a scarf by hand.
どうしたら渡せるんだろう
How can I give it to you?
意気地なし 怖かっただけ
I'm such a coward, I was just scared.
思い出になるなら
If it's only going to be a memory,
このままで構わないって
I told myself I didn't care if it stayed like this...
そっと魔法をかけた
...and softly cast a spell.
ありがとう さようなら
Thank you, goodbye.
いつかこんな時が
I always knew that someday...
来てしまうこと わかってたはずだわ
...a time like this would come.
なのに
And yet...
ありがとう さようなら
Thank you, goodbye.
体中が震えてる
My entire body is trembling.
もうすぐ列車が来るのに
Even though the train will be here soon...
それは今になって
...that truth only now...
私を苦しめる
...begins to torment me.
繋がりたい
I want to be connected to you.
どれほど願っただろう
How much did I wish for that?
この手はからっぽ
Yet, these hands of mine are empty.
ねえ
Hey...
さよならって
...does saying "goodbye"...
sそういうこと？
...really mean this?
行かなくちゃ
I have to go.
そんなのわかってる
I already know that.
キミが優しいことも知ってる
I know how kind you are, too.
だから
That's why...
この手を離してよ
...please let go of my hand.
出会えてよかった
I'm so glad I met you.
キミが好き
I love you.
ありがとう さようなら
Thank you, goodbye.
一言が言えない
I can't say that one single word.
今だけでいい 私に勇気を
Just for now, please give me courage.
あのね
You see...
凍えそうな唇
...on these freezing lips,
キミとの距離はゼロ
...the distance between us is zero.
今だけは泣いていいよね
I can cry just for now, right?
もう言葉はいらない
No more words are needed.
お願い ぎゅっとしていて
Please, hold me tight.
来年の今頃には
Around this time next year,
どんな私がいて
what kind of person will I be,
どんなキミがいるのかな
and what kind of person will you be?
Whoa, you got some extensions?
Extensions? I don't remember
getting anything like that, really.
Your hair is even longer!
Heh, it's fashionable though, don't you think?
It looks kind of familiar.
Like, maybe we're missing...
Oh!
Oh, you have another arm too?
Whoa, there, hold on a second.
Something's kind of strange.
Are you growing up?
Not only have the seasons changed...
Ah! I lost Calli!
...but it looks like we've lost somebody.
Ina! / Welcome back!
Hi. Hello.
You're here, you're here.
Nice! Nice, nice hair! / Nice hair.
The seasons have changed.
Yes, it's getting a little warmer, thank goodness.
It was kind of cool, though.
Just a little chilly,
especially for me and Kiara's song.
Spring! Yeah, it's become spring.
Oh, beautiful!
Whoa, check it out, the stage is so pink!
I actually really love the color pink,
now that I'm 16.
Oh! Oh! / Character development!
The seasons have changed.
That's good, that's good.
Wow, pretty!
And we're wearing yukata, kimono,
whatever you want it to be.
And we all went with kind of a blue color, huh?
Yeah, we do look like we're about
to drop a sweet enka album.
This is how they pose.
Dokkoisho, dokkoisho! / Dokkoisho, dokkoisho!
Soran, soran, soran, soran!
Okay, that's not what we're doing.
That's not what we're releasing, though.
So we did a bunch of songs.
Yeah. / Like, for example?
For example...
Step and Go, do you remember?
That's not the one that you sang!
No, please, please, but this is a
really iconic old Japanese song, okay?
They did a lot of posing.
...
It was so cute. I hope you guys enjoyed this old tune.
Yeah, right?
Ina, did you know it before?
No.
Calli, did you know it before?
No? First time hearing it.
I think everyone in the chat will also agree...
When we hear the word September, we think...
No, no, no! This is how we change the impression of September!
When we say September, you guys won't think of that September anymore.
You'll think about this September with me and Ina, okay?
Yeah, just for now. / Yeah!
What else did we perform?
Oh, I also saw you did some ballet skating moves.
Ooh! Are you a filthy archer? I'm disgusted.
You hate archer? / I hate archer. Archer hater.
But she was a kenshi! / They're such cheaters!
I've never seen this anime, but is there actually an archer in there?
Yeah. / Really? / No. Oh, no.
There are skaters though.
Oh, skaters! Skaters. Figure skaters.
They can skate?
Oh, I can! I can do it. I'm all right.
I can skate too. / Okay, here we go.
Really? We should go! We should go! I can ice skate!
Promise. / That was my favorite hobby when I was younger.
It's a promise. / Mhm.
Anyway, I loved your low tones. / Yes! Thank you!
Your whispers were really hot. / No, no, no, it came out beautifully. You sounded wonderful.
Oh, thank you.
And then, I got to sing with Kiara as the snow fell.
Yes! Yay!
We talked and sang a song about first love, and... / It was so cute! Weren't we so cute?
This is just what happens when first love ends.
Aww! Te-te!
This is so... feels wholesome to me, I don't know.
We held hands and... / Kiss. Kiss.
How did that make you feel, everybody in the chat?
Were you jealous, or were you happy for us? / What did you think about first love ends?
Think carefully about your answer.
Were you happy for us? Totally, okay. Thank you.
They're definitely saying yes. / Yeah!
Well, we have also changed costumes. / Yes!
Blue! / We're so blue!
White and pink. White, blue, pink. / Yeah.
Red, white and blue. / Red, white, and blue! Not quite.
We've got goldfish, kingyo, and blue. / Mizu-iro. Cuz I've got purple puffs.
Ah, so da ne! So da ne. / There's a bit of purple... Wait, is this morning glory?
Ah, I thought they were jellyfish.
Are they jellyfish? / No, I think it's morning... morning glory!
It could be... it could also be Austrian bread. Austrian bread.
That's exactly the shape of Austrian bread.
Yeah, do the breads come in those colors? / No, unless they're moldy!
Oh la la, hope you never eat one of those. / Don't eat moldy bread.
Yeah, we know you're aware of this. / Have you eaten moldy bread before, everybody? No? Are you sure?
Stale, stale bread. / Why is this what we're talking about during our concert?
It's okay, a little whimsy is fine. But now how about we get serious for a moment...
...and sing a kyoku, song.
A kyoku! Let's sing a kyoku. / English Jouzu.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
We'll sing a song that's a little bit emoi.
I was listening to the lyrics and practicing it, and I was like, "Hmm, you know, there are a couple of lyrics here and there..."
"...that remind me of, like, the struggles that we have gone through and how I want to go forward with you guys."
So, it made me kind of like... emoi. So, I hope we can sing it well together.
We will! We will! / We'll do it. In these slightly restrictive...
...but they're really stretchy. / Okay.
All right, enough of that.
Yeah, you like that? I like that. / Well... / All right, positions!
Shall we? Shall we dance and sing?
All right! / Listen to our next song, Suzume.
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la...
君の中にある 赤と青き線
The red and blue lines inside of you
それらが結ばれるのは 心の臓
Where they connect is at your heart
風の中でも負けないような声で
With a voice that won't lose to the wind
届ける言葉を今は育ててる
I'm nurturing the words I will deliver to you now
時はまくらぎ
Time is a sleeper
風はにきはだ
The wind is soft skin
星はうぶすな
The stars are our birthplace,
人はかげろう
and humans are but shadows.
なんで泣いてるの と聞かれ答えれる
When asked why I'm crying, I can answer...
涙なんかじゃ
with something more than tears.
僕ら出逢えたことの意味にはまるで
The meaning of our meeting doesn't even...
追いつかない
...compare.
この身ひとつじゃ
With just this one body...
足りない叫び
...it's an insufficient cry.
君の手触れた時にだけ震えた
Only when our hands touched did it tremble,
心があったよ
proving there was a heart.
意味をいくつか越えれば僕らは辿り
After crossing several meanings, will we arrive...
着けるのかな
...at our destination?
愚かさでいい
Even foolishness is fine,
醜さでいい
even ugliness is fine.
正しさのその先で
Beyond what is right,
君と手を取りたい
I want to take your hand.
思い出せない
I can't remember...
大切な記憶
...that precious memory.
言葉にならない
They won't become words...
ここにある思い
...these feelings I have right here.
もしかしたら
Perhaps...
...perhaps...
それだけでこの心はできてる
...my heart is made of nothing but that.
もしかしたら
Perhaps...
...perhaps...
君に気づいてと今も
...begging you to notice,
その胸を
...on your chest,
打ち鳴らす
...it keeps beating.
なんで泣いてるの と聞かれ答えれる
When asked why I'm crying, I can answer...
涙なんかじゃ
with something more than tears.
僕ら出逢えたことの意味にはまるで
The meaning of our meeting doesn't even...
追いつかない
...compare.
この身ひとつじゃ
With just this one body...
足りない叫び
...it's an insufficient cry.
君の手触れた時にだけ震えた
Only when our hands touched did it tremble,
心があったよ
proving there was a heart.
意味をいくつか越えれば僕らは辿り
After crossing several meanings, will we arrive...
着けるのかな
...at our destination?
愚かさでいい
Even foolishness is fine,
醜さでいい
even ugliness is fine.
正しさのその先で
Beyond what is right,
君と生きていきたい
I want to live with you.
SAKURA Days (feat. AO)
離れる黒さと 晒される すべてが恋しい
I miss the departing darkness and all that is exposed,
セピアの心情 開いては
opening my sepia feelings...
また思いふける
...I lose myself in thought again.
SAKURA Days
満ちてゆく風に
In the rising wind,
揺れるただ髪が懐かしい
as my hair simply sways, I feel nostalgic.
賑わいと温もりを運んでくれた
It brought me bustle and warmth.
おかげで色づいた花
Thanks to that, the flowers have colored.
あるものは恋焦がれて
Some are burning with love,
あるものはみんなで分かち合い
some are sharing it with everyone.
千の眼差しを
While receiving...
受けるものの
...a thousand gazes.
舞い散る
Fluttering down...
夜風に
...in the night wind,
触れば刹那香わし
touching it makes it momentarily fragrant.
サヨナラとありがとうを共に送るよ
I send both a farewell and a thank you.
おかげでまた好きになった
Thanks to that, I fell in love with it again.
去るものを追うはずなく
There is no point in chasing those who leave
来るものを拒めるわけない
And no way to refuse those who come
ゆえに尊い
And so, it is precious...
桜色の日々よ
These cherry blossom-colored days
離れる覚悟 さとらせる全てが愛おしい
Preparing to say goodbye, everything that reminds me of it is lovely
セピアの心情を開いては
Opening up these sepia emotions...
また想い耽る
...I lose myself in thought once again
SAKURA Days
遥か彼方響く君の声に耳をすませば
If I listen closely to your voice echoing from far away...
少なからずその温もり思い出せるよ
...without fail, I can recall that warmth
凛とした寂しさも風情と成る
Even this crisp loneliness becomes charming
SAKURA Days
SAKURA Days...
少なからずその温もり思い出せるよ
Without fail, I can recall that warmth
麗しき SAKURA Days
These beautiful SAKURA Days
[本気ボンバー！！]
[Title: Honki Bomber!!]
夏じゃん！
It's summer!
見上げる空 青い海
Looking up at the sky, the blue ocean
WOW WOW
自由に描こう
Let's draw freely!
僕がルール
I make the rules!
OH YEAH!
夏JUMP!
Summer JUMP!
大きくなれ 本気ボンバー
Grow bigger, Honki Bomber!
WOW WOW
好奇心のまま GO!
Go with your curiosity!
熱くなれ！
Get fired up!
遊びも100
Playing 100%!
学びも100
Learning 100%!
力いっぱい
With all our might!
手を抜かない ボンバー
We won't hold back, Bomber!
クヨクヨのせいには 絶対しない
Never going to blame things on feeling down!
そもそも人生一回きりの連続
After all, life is a series of one-time chances!
夏じゃん！
It's summer!
頼れる奴 キザなヤツ
A reliable guy, a show-off guy
WOW WOW
いろいろ出会い
All kinds of encounters...
僕が育つ
...make me grow!
OH YEAH!
夏JUMP!
Summer JUMP!
成長しろ 本気ボンバー
Go grow up, Honki Bomber!
WOW WOW
世界みんなで Peace!
Peace for everyone in the world!
立ち上がれ！
Stand up!
涙も出る
Tears will fall
拍手もする
We will applaud
褒めて褒められ
Praising and being praised
やる気も出る ボンバー
Motivating us, Bomber!
カブトムシだって 夢があるだろう
Even beetles must have dreams, right?
いつかは大空の彼方 飛んじゃうじゃん
One day they will fly far into the wide sky!
夏じゃん！
It's summer!
見上げる空 青い海
Looking up at the sky, the blue ocean
WOW WOW
自由に描こう
Let's draw freely!
僕がルール
I make the rules!
OH YEAH!
夏JUMP!
Summer JUMP!
大きくなれ 本気ボンバー
Grow bigger, Honki Bomber!
WOW WOW
好奇心のまま GO!
Go with your curiosity!
熱くなれ！
Get fired up!
イェイ！
Yeah!
夏じゃん！
It's summer!
頼れる奴 キザなヤツ
A reliable guy, a show-off guy
WOW WOW
いろいろ出会い
All kinds of encounters...
僕が育つ
...make me grow!
OH YEAH!
夏JUMP!
Summer JUMP!
成長しろ 本気ボンバー
Go grow up, Honki Bomber!
WOW WOW
世界みんなで Peace!
Peace for everyone in the world!
立ち上がれ！
Stand up!
夏じゃん！
It's summer!
見上げる空 青い海
Looking up at the sky, the blue ocean
WOW WOW
自由に描こう
Let's draw freely!
僕がルール
I make the rules!
OH YEAH!
レッツJUMP！
Let's jump!
大きくなれ 本気ボンバー！
Grow bigger, Real Bomber!
WOW WOW
好奇心のまま GO！
Go with your curiosity, go!
熱くなれ！
Fire up!
YO! SAY 夏が 胸を刺激する
Yo, say! The summer stimulates my chest,
ナマ足 魅惑の マーメイド
a mesmerizing mermaid with bare legs.
出すとこ出して たわわになったら
Show off what you've got, and when it's ripe...
宝物の恋は やれ 爽快っ
The love we treasure will feel so refreshing!
ゴマカシきかない 薄着の曲線は
No hiding the curves under these light clothes,
確信犯の しなやかな STYLE!
a deliberate and supple style!
耐水性の 気持ちに切り替わる
Switching my feelings to a waterproof mindset...
瞬間(とき)の眩しさは いかがなもの
How about the dazzling radiance of this moment?
ココロまで脱がされる
Even my heart is laid bare...
熱い風の誘惑に
by the temptation of the hot breeze.
負けちゃって構わないから
I don't mind giving in to it,
真夏は 不祥事も キミ次第で
since midsummer scandals are all up to you.
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
The fairies stimulate the summer,
ナマ足 魅惑の マーメイド
a mesmerizing mermaid with bare legs.
出すとこ出して たわわになったら
Show off what you've got, and when it's ripe...
宝物の恋が できそうかい?
think we can find our treasured love?
キミじゃなくても バテ気味にもなるよ
Even if it's not you, anyone would get worn out.
暑いばっかの 街は憂鬱で
A city that's only hot is so depressing.
隙を見せたら 不意に耳に入る
If you let your guard down, you'll suddenly hear...
サブイギャグなんかで 涼みたくない
and I don't want to cool off with lame jokes.
むせ返る熱帯夜を
The sweltering tropical night,
彩る花火のように
like the fireworks that color it...
打ち上げて散る想いなら
If these feelings are to shoot up and scatter...
このまま抱き合って 焦がれるまで
let's hold each other until we burn.
妖精たちと 夏をしたくなる
I want to spend summer with fairies,
熱い欲望は トルネイド
our hot desires spinning like a tornado.
出すもの出して 素直になりたい
Let's put everything out there and be honest,
キミとボクとなら IT'S ALL RIGHT
because if it's you and me, it's all right!
都会(まち)のビルの海じゃ
In this sea of city buildings,
感じなくなってる キミを
you've lost all of your feelings.
冷えきった永遠(とわ)のくちづけで
With a freezing, eternal kiss...
酔わせて 蕩(とろ)かして 差し上げましょう
let me intoxicate and melt you away.
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
The fairies stimulate the summer,
ナマ足 ヘソ出し マーメイド
a midriff-baring mermaid with bare legs.
恋に負けて お留守になるのも
Losing to love and zoning out...
ダイスキ的にも オールオッケー
is totally okay in my book!
妖精夏を 誰としたくなる
Who do you want to spend this magical summer with?
一人きりの夜に ユー・キヤン・セイ・グッバイ
To lonely nights, you can say goodbye!
奥の方まで 乾く間ないほど
To the point where we won't even dry inside...
本気の恋を しませんか?
won't you fall in a passionate love with me?
Whoa! Woo! Yeah!
Ina gets more center!
Yes. Yeah.
Super Sentai?
I don't know, maybe that's our Super Sentai move.
No, no, no, no!
No, like this... No, it was sexy.
Okay, sexy, sexy Sentai!
Sexy Sentai, yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sexy, sexy, sexy.
Oh, where did we go? Okay, welcome back everybody!
Hey! Welcome back! Hello!
What did you guys think? Have a good time?
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Did some awesome songs.
Yeah. So many good songs.
Yeah, some very close to my heart.
HOT LIMIT...
Very HOT LIMIT... HOT LIMIT hotness.
Why did you choose that song?
We're already...
...too hot. You were...
Yeah, already too hot, yeah.
Past the hot.
Makes sense.
Yeah, absolutely.
If you were on the stage, everything would have lit on fire.
Yeah, there's a lot of trees here, how about them?
I don't know, if we die, it will be bad.
And I did my solo, Maji Bamba, which is a Hello! Project song.
I had to squeeze in one more Hello! Project song.
I hope you like it. Some people might know it because it's also an anime opening, maybe.
Whoa!
Yeah, maybe some people recognized it.
You know?
And you did a solo?
I did, I did. 'Sakuradays'...
...because...
...that song is a song that I did at my very first ever singing stream six years ago.
And I could not...
...the pitches was like, I either sang it super low or super high.
...the pitch was like, I either sang it super low or super high.
And this time I was like, "I want to really sing it with my whole heart."
So that song is really special to me, and I hope you guys enjoyed "Sakuradays".
Ohh!
Enough of that.
And then, that was such a good reaction.
Okay, who's next? Shift the focus.
I don't know, I don't know. What was next? "Sisume"?
We did "Sisume".
That was a lot of fun.
Oh yeah, really beautiful.
Yeah, we looked really cool together, and the stage was lovely as well.
And we went through some next seasons, right?
We did. We went through summer.
We're in summer right now, I don't know.
It's a little hot, so probably.
Definitely summer! It's going to cool down from now, you guys, definitely.
Or will it get even hotter?
Oh my god!
Perhaps this was a sign.
Okay, this is, however, a PR section, isn't it?
We have to. We have to show something to you guys, right?
So, first and foremost, I'll start, I'll start.
Oh, it's okay, don't everybody all go at once. I will begin.
So, first of all, as you guys know, I had my own little solo show in VR.
And at that time, I promoted to you guys...
...this year's Mori Calliope 6th Anniversary Goods!
Yay!
Check them out, check them out!
Whoa! Can I join in? Whoa!
No, no, no, no!
All right, I feel left out right now, but that's okay, we can go on.
So, okay, good idea.
So, if you are a fan of Mori Calliope, Dead Beat, I'm looking at you.
I have an official Happi coming out, it's my very first Happi!
It's really cool. I wanted to emphasize something that's very cool, like...
...cool darkness, and there's the illustration of me on the back, looks like a painting, it's really cool.
Very illustrative, not quite... it's like it's half... and we have very illustrative...
So, I hope that you like it, there's a big skull on the front, it's awesome!
Yeah, and then...
Dead Beat's official headband, because I know you guys...
They finally get their headband!
Headband, yay! Official Dead Beat headband!
And then, also, in addition to that, I have a bag.
Bag! That has...
A bag? What color is the bag?
Black, of course.
And it's got a little window in it, you can carry one of my badges.
A window? Black with a window?
Yes, yes, black with a window.
And, penlight holder!
Penlight holder, very important! And a little place where you can put your badges.
And I have four random badges that you can get.
A random one, or you can just try and buy all of them.
Okay.
But I hope you are very lucky.
In addition to that, so yeah, please buy the goods. Buy them. And yeah.
So that's what I have for goods.
Now, also, my latest music video 'Reimei Compass'...
...is out right now.
So, I have a brand new 3D outfit.
I do lots of dancing.
I have some cool backup dancers that are real people behind me, so it's really cool.
Real people?
Yeah, and it's Mori in the real world, and I also... I'm really big. I'm like a kaiju, also.
So it's really awesome.
Yes.
So, please make sure you watch that. And also finally, Chadcast has begun again.
Yay! Hooray!
Yes, me and IRyS and Bae, we also have a music video for our theme song too.
So don't miss out on that.
That's all that I have for PR.
Oh, that's all?
That's really it. Are you sure there's more?
That's really it. I know there's a lot of stuff. Sorry!
Let's go to Ina.
Ina, your turn, Ina.
Well, I just revealed... or I guess last week...
...revealed my new outfit!
It's so pretty!
Yeah.
And with that, I also released my 6th Anniversary Merch!
Yay!
Very elegant.
And of course, everyone... yeah, we have cup and saucer.
A cup and saucer!
It's fancy, a cup of tea.
Or you can put coffee in it too.
Does it fit cookies?
Yeah, and then there's a mini plushie of me in my new outfit.
Mini Ina!
And of course, I like a little bit of randomness in my life, so some random...
- Rubber keychain! - Rubber keychain!
- Random, random! - And a beautiful...
- ...acrylic block. - Acrylic block!
Yeah! Thank you, thank you!
- Y'all, let's go! Yeah! - And of course,
last but not least... very final project! Finally!
At last, at last! Our Abyssal Hymn EP!
Yes! Let's go!
Go check it out. Very high quality,
beautiful, beautiful, don't miss out. Yes.
It's releasing... to be released.
I don't know. Ah!
This is past us. It's probably out.
- It's probably out. - Likely out.
- Well, maybe, yeah. - Big chance it's out.
If it's out, watch it. If not, get ready!
Get ready! That's right, okay.
And last but not least...
- Kiara! - Takanashi Kiara!
This year has no anniversary merchandise,
no solo and no group, so I have nothing!
I also don't have a song coming out either.
- Wait, wait! - It's okay.
There's a gift from you guys to me, and from me
to me, which is I'm taking a break. Thank you!
- Take a good rest. Come back strong. - Yeah.
Please welcome me back when I do come back.
And please wait for me. Don't forget about me.
But you can still support me in a way by
supporting all of us because we now finally can
say we have a new song coming out! We will
perform it now, and it will premiere after this.
We will raid you, but in case the raid doesn't
work, make sure to jump in there. It's on this channel.
- Yeah, it's on this channel. - 99% sure.
- Are you excited? - Get hyped, get hyped!
They are excited, I can sense. It's very cool.
Hold on, wearing this outfit does not mean we
have to move a lot. Yeah! Oh yeah! Bring it around.
A little preview! Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
So, are you ready? I know you can do it, Ina.
- Let's do it! - Breathe, breathe.
- Mori. - Ina.
This is Myth!
Yeah! Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Yeah? Stay for the premiere, guys.
THIS IS MYTH
Stand up, shout it, ask the audience
Do y'all feel it?
Start up havoc, go on, take a guess
Yeah, what's the name? Myth!
Been here from the start, we laid the groundwork
Had a spark, now look, it's an inferno
No, no, won't say sorry, we paved the way
Built it from zero, you get the memo?
Mythologically, you're still tryna figure out
How my mind navigates where you couldn't, yeah
Try and find what we about
But know ya goin' down
It's destiny, it's
It's not a stroke of luck
Can't you see that
it was meant to be?
Go shout the name out, yeah you know just what to do
If you want us, say it loud like
M-Y-T-H
Hit the SOS, call the crowd in
We the best, the rest can't imagine
How pretty I'm sittin' here up at the top
Goin' nonstop, show ya what we got
Make ya stressed, I bet you been sweatin'
What's our next move? We'll leave you guessin'
We don't trip up and we never stop
Had to remind ya in case you forgot
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh
Now and then, we the best! So, yell it like... Myth!
I can hear 'em... This is our myth!
It ain't a surprise that we pulled up, took the win
From the very start, made the biggest impression
Now we got crowds begging for us on stage
Yelling out loud, "MYTH!" They'd all die for me
We unstoppable, it's our reputation
You can bet on forever, we ain't done
Come try and find what we about
But know ya goin' down
It's destiny, it's
It's not a stroke of luck
Can't you see that
it was meant to be?
Go shout the name out, yeah you know just what to do
If you want us, say it loud like
M-Y-T-H
Hit the SOS, call the crowd in
We the best, the rest can't imagine
How pretty I'm sittin' here up at the top
Goin' nonstop, show ya what we got
We the best, the rest can't imagine
How pretty I'm sittin' here up at the top
How pretty I'm sitting here up at the top
Goin' nonstop, show you what we got
Going nonstop, showing you what we've got
Make ya stressed, I bet you sweating
Make you stressed, I bet you're sweating
What's our next move? We'll leave you guessing
We don't trip up and we never stop
Had to remind ya in case you forgot
Had to remind you in case you forgot
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh
Now and then, we the best, so yell it alive
Now and then, we're the best, so yell it alive
MYTH!
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh
I can hear 'em go...
I can hear them go...
This is our MYTH!
Thanks a lot, everyone!
See ya! Stay tuned...
...for the music video! おねがい！
...for the music video! Please!
We're raiding you!